<details open="true">
    <summary><h3 class="integration">Integration and Delivery</h3></summary>  
      <a name="integration"> </a>
        <p>
            Integration and delivery for HIV Screening involves the usage of reasoning as a service (or on-demand data ingestion) to deliver computational expressions for a clinical practice guideline. This mechanism of integration is utilized for the HIV Screening guidelines through the usage of CDS-Hooks to provide clinical decision support for a clinician's workflow.
        </p>

        <a name="serviceingestion"> </a>
        <h4>Reasoning-as-a-Service (on-demand data ingest and insight/inference delivery)</h4>

            <p>
                Integration of inferences or insights as a Service is similarly discussed in the related Methods of Implementation.  
                In this pattern, there is some trigger (e.g. user interface event) in the clinical information system (or application of use) that prompts the system to call a Clinical Reasoning Service that provides the execution capability for the computable representations of the clinical practice guideline.  
                The application of record/use may require multiple “round trips” to get the clinical reasoning service the data required to make appropriate inferences and then to receive those inferences.  
                The service may directly provide inferences as data elements, may return a presentation layer (e.g., html), may return a link (href) to launch an external application (e.g. SMART-on-FHIR), or some combination of all three.  
                Of note, this pattern of integration is typically implemented as on-demand or just-in-time service calls, clinical reasoning, and inference/insight delivery. CDSHooks is a principle example of this pattern.
            </p>

            <div>
                <img alt="Clinical Reasoning-as-a-Service" class="img-responsive img-rounded center-block" src="{{site.data.info.assets}}integration-content-service.png"/>
            </div>

            <p><em>Figure 3</em> An example and pattern of Clinical Reasoning-as-a-Service using CDS Hooks eventing, 'pre-fetch' of patient data, and response.</p>

            Sourced from the <a href="http://build.fhir.org/ig/HL7/cqf-recommendations/documentation-approach-10-mechanisms-of-integration.html"> FHIR Clinical Guidelines IG. </a>
</details>
